bustersports.com 2009-12-24

# Privacy Policy > Buster Sports

This is the Privacy Policy for the United States of America. 

Thank you for visiting Buster Sports Communications, Inc. site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Buster Sports Communications, Inc. 

**The Information We Collect**  
Through Buster Sports Communications, Inc. publications, websites, and other media, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. You are able to visit much of this website and enjoy many Buster Sports Communications, Inc. publications and promotions without providing any personally identifiable information. Sometimes, however, we do need your personally identifiable information to provide you with the products and services that you request. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages and elsewhere include, but are not limited to: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

For certain promotions, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the promotion's activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. 

**How We Use the Information**  
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your name, screen name, and other information you have provided to us.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and websites and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Agents and contractors of Buster Sports Communications, Inc. who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Buster Sports Communications, Inc.

We may transfer your personally identifiable information to other Buster Sports Communications, Inc. offices for internal management and administrative purposes. Your personal data will be transferred to other Buster Sports Communications, Inc. offices where necessary for the performance or conclusion of our contractual obligations to you or for your benefit. Transfers of personally identifiable information may also be made where necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data. 

**Privacy Options**  
If a Buster Sports Communications, Inc. site discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by Buster Sports Communications, Inc. who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses.

Buster Sports Communications, Inc. may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive online marketing information from this or any other Buster Sports Communications, Inc. site, please contact us.

Buster Sports Communications, Inc. sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses. 

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**  
Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Buster Sports Communications, Inc. sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. Buster Sports

Communications, Inc. has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. The Buster Sports Communications, Inc. site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.

Buster Sports Communications, Inc. sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. This privacy notice does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). 

**Cookies**  
To enhance your online experience we use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings, and advertisements. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. Similarly, as part of an arrangement with our business partners (including, those who present or serve the advertisements that you see on our web pages) we may also access cookies placed by others and allow others to access certain cookies placed by us.

We may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy. 

**Our Commitment to Security**  
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect.   
**  
How You can Access or Correct Information**   
To inquire about personally identifiable information that this Buster Sports Communications, Inc. site has collected about you, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please contact Buster Sports Communications, Inc.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

Changes to this Notice This Notice may be changed by Buster Sports Communications, Inc. The revised Notice will be posted to this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. 

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the Buster Sports Communications, Inc. Privacy Notice or its implementation please contact us via email at Service@bustersports.com or at the following address: 

Buster Sports Communications   
Attention: Customer Service   
2210 East Millbrook Road   
Suite 115   
Raleigh, North Carolina 27604
